

CONTACT



(+91) 7478284428



arkya22@gmail.com



Kolkata, West Bengal, India



Bangalore, Karnataka, India



linkedin.com/in/arkyasantra-3bb475175



https://github.com/masc4424

SKILLS

MS Word, MS Excel & MS Power Point

C,C++,Python & Java



Java Script, HTML,PHP, CSS & SQL



VIDEO EDITING & IMAGE EDITING



LANGUAGES



HINDI



BENGALI - - -

HOBBIES







ARKYA SANTRA

An enthusiastic Electronics and Communication Engineer with experience in projects based in AI and IoT as well as training in Python, JAVA, C & C++ and also experienced in Web Development in possession of strong communication and leadership skills.

EDUCATION

B. Tech Electronics and Communication. 2018-2022 Adamas University, Kolkata, India

- Member of IETE Kolkata Region.
- Received 2nd prize in Techx 2019 organized by ADAMAS UNIVERSITY.
- Published a paper on "UWB Antenna with Bandwidth Enhancement for 5G, IOT, USB-dongle and UWB Wireless Applications" || Journal named: IEEE Xplore.
- Project: Home automation using Node MCU.
- Project: College Management System Android App and Website.
- Marks: 8.84 CGPA

Higher Secondary Education (10+2) 2017-2018 Kendriya Vidyalaya, West Bengal, India

- Received 1st Prize in English Spelling Competition
- Marks: 51%

Secondary Education (10)

2014-2015

Kendriya Vidyalaya, Tamil Nadu, India

Marks: 6.8 CGPA

EXPERIENCE

Student Intern

Feb 2021-March 2021

CoreEL Tech., Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

- Successfully completed the internship on Functional Verification using SystemVerilog.
- Completed the Project on Carry Skip adder using System Verilog.

Student Intern

July 2021-Aug 2021

The Sparks Found., Singapore

- Successfully completed the internship on Web Development.
- Completed the Project on making a Basic Banking System.

Student Intern

June 2021-Aug 2021

Spotle.AI, Kolkata, India

- Successfully completed the internship on Spotle.ai NASSCOM Community AI.
- Completed the Project on Analyse Crop Production